

#### **PROFILE**

I am a driven data scientist, data engineer, AI researcher and robotics developer. Programming and working with computers in general has been a passion for quite some time.

In love with automation and minimizing repetitive work, which is why I'm able to focus on efficient & application-oriented learning, developing and problem solving.

Switching views, working on agile projects and changing approaches often motivate me to study new topics, tackle hard challenges and deliver results.

# **BIRTHDATE**

11 januari 2000

# **ADDRESS**

Houthalen-Helchteren, Belgium

# PHONE NUMBER

+32486539354

# MAILING ADDRESS

kobethuwis26@gmail.com

#### **PORTFOLIO**

https://kobethuwis.github.io/

# KOBE THUWIS

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

InfoFarm: Junior data engineer/data scientist 2021 – Present

### Lineas Data Squad

Lineas is the largest private rail freight operator in Europe. I develop and setup Kubernetes clusters, AWS data pools and NiFi data flows using Terraform and custom configuration scripts, in order to provide a singular, central data storage and management platform.

### • ANPR Big Data Platform

The ANPR Big Data Platform is a scalable and extensible platform for collecting, storing and aggregating ANPR data. My task within the project is to construct a big data lake using AWS and make the data usable for analysis, reporting and future processing.

## PXL Smart ICT: Research & Development Intern 2021

ArtiFISHal Intelligence is a twofold project, consisting of scenes made in Unity which illustrate several reinforcement learning techniques. Secondly, the project contains a simulation of a marine ecosystem which uses state of the art evolutionary algorithms.

Chiro Meulenberg: Head Monitor 2018 - Present

**Strandbal: Event Manager** 2018 - Present **Youth Council Member** 2019 - Present

# **EDUCATION**

### 2018-2021: Hogeschool PXL

Bachelor in Applied Information Technology with a specialisation in Artificial Intelligence (AI) & robotics.

### 2012-2018: Kindsheid Jesu

High school diploma in Maths & Sciences